musiccitynetworks.com 2013-03-27

# Privacy Policy | Music City Networks

**Privacy Policy**

**MusicCityNetworks, LLC ("MCN")** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our, and our clients', website visitors, online community participants, and fan club members. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for websites hosted by MCN (the "website"). If you choose not to consent to this Privacy Statement, you may not use these websites. Further, this policy is subject to change at any time with or without notice at the sole discretion of MCN, so you should re-read it periodically.

**1\. How We Use Collected Information**  

_Server Logs._

Our servers record your computer's IP address and website usage in "server logs" when you use the websites. No personally identifiable information is contained in these logs, such as name, address, phone numbers or email addresses. We use these logs to help diagnose problems with our servers, analyze traffic patterns and to administer the websites.

_Cookies._  
We use cookies on certain pages of our websites. Cookies are small text files stored on your hard drive, not on our websites. A cookie is not a program, and does not itself have the ability to automatically collect personal information about you. A cookie can store certain information that identifies your browser to our servers in order to make the websites operate more smoothly. For example, we use cookies to aid in the functioning of the shopping cart and sign in form. Most cookies we use are "session cookies" which means that they are automatically deleted when you leave the websites. Some of our advertising partners may also use cookies. We do not have access to or control over such cookies.

_Registration._  
If you choose to register with our websites, our registration forms require you to give us certain information including your name, address, zip/postal code, phone number, email address, and date of birth. Personally identifying information is used to contact you when necessary in the day to day running of the websites. In addition, financial information that is collected is used to bill you for products and services you may purchase through the websites.

_Voluntary Contact._  
If you send us information voluntarily, such as through personal correspondence, email, or chat rooms, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our websites, we may collect such information. We use such information, and other information that we obtain from your use of the services, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Acceptable Use Policy, among other things. Please also note that information you volunteer in public areas, such as chat rooms and bulletin boards, is not protected information, and anyone could potentially collect and use such information in ways we cannot control.  

In addition to using your information as described above, we also may occasionally send you email announcing special promotions, changes in our services, and other information we believe will be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any future mailings by clicking on " **opt out using TrueRemove™** " located at the bottom of all emails sent via MCN email marketing.  

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances without your consent, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. However, we will not use your information for marketing purposes outside of the sites you have registered for. We do not sell or rent our list of users past or present to any third party without your consent.  

**2\. Linked Websites**  
For your convenience, the websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that MCN and our client sites are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites, which may differ significantly from our own. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our websites and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our websites.  

**3\. Security**  
The websites have procedural security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Only authorized individuals have access to your information. On all pages where user credit card information is entered, we utilize a secure digital server, with a secure certificate from VeriSign. Notwithstanding these efforts, we caution you that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.  

**4\. A Special Note About Children**  
This website is a general audience site and is not directed to or intended for use by children under the age of 13.  To ensure compliance with federal law, this website does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information provided by children under the age of 13.  If a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information in violation of the website access restrictions, a parent or guardian of that child must contact us immediately at [info@MusicCityNetworks.com](mailto://info@musiccitynetworks.com/) so we can promptly remove such information from our records. 

**5.** **Your California Privacy Rights**  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

**Online Privacy Coordinator**  
MusicCityNetworks  
209 Tenth Avenue South, Suite 400  
Nashville, TN 37203

**6.** **Contacting Us** **  
** If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this websites, or your dealings with these websites, you may email us at [info@MusicCityNetworks.com ](mailto://info@musiccitynetworks.com/).
